blog-search.com 2017-09-15

# Privacy Policy - Blog-Search.com

This Privacy Policy covers the Blog Search treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit your blog for inclusion in our database. Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the Blog Search web site, nor does it extend to people that Blog Search does not employ or manage.

### Information Collection and Use

Blog Search offers free Standard Blog listings and paid inclusion Featured Listings. The information we collect is dependent on your needs.

For Standard Blog submissions, the only information collected is Name, Email Address, IP Address and the date of your submission. Additional information is collected for Featured Site listings, but these can only be purchased at ExactSeek.com.

Your use of Blog Search services (standard or featured listing) constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your blog(s). In exchange, Blog Search reserves the right to use the contact information collected during blog submission to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide free sample newsletters, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information from our partners.

With the exception of auto-response messages which are sent at the time of blog submission and which contain important confirmation details regarding your blog listing, you may remove yourself from any or all other notice and announcement mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes at least 2 methods to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact [inquiry[at]blog-search.com](mailto:inquiry\[at\]blog-search.com). Our turnaround time for responding to unsubscribe requests is generally 24 hours.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Blog Search maintains your email address and other pertinent personal information, provided at the time of your blog submission, on the premises. Blog Search allows carefully screened vendors the opportunity to send you offers and information that we have deemed may be of value to you. You may opt-in or out of this feature at any time.

### Cookies

Cookies must be enabled to use Blog Search

### Security

Your personal information is stored in a protected database. Access is restricted to Blog Search staff.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Blog Search may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change. 

### Questions or Suggestions

Questions or suggestions may be sent to: [inquiry[at]blog-search.com](mailto:inquiry\[at\]blog-search.com).

To prevent address harvesting, the "@" symbol in the email addresses above have been replaced with [at]. If you wish to contact us, simply copy the appropri ate address into your email client and replace [at] with @.
